Whoop. Heads up, gang.
哇哦  注意了  伙计们
Looks like we're about to stop at our first town.
看来我们要在第一个城镇歇脚了
My first town outside of Wartwood.
我在树瘤丛林外遇到的第一个城镇
I wonder what it'll be like.
不知道会是什么样子
Will the frogs be friendly? Will they have a bathroom?
这里的青蛙友好吗  他们有浴室吗
Don't get too excited, Anne.
别太激动了  小安
It's just your average small town.
这只是一个普通的小镇
Pssh, how small can it be... Wow!
切  能有多小  哇
Oh, my gosh.
噢  天哪
It's literally a small town.
真的是一个很小的小镇
Just look at the "wittle" buildings.
看看这些萌萌的建筑
There you are, girl.
来吧  姑娘
What's all the ruckus?
怎么这么吵
B-but, please. Just listen.
但  但是  请听我说
Ooh. I gotcha.
哦  我接住你了
All right. Y'all know the rules.
好吧  你们都知道规矩
Pay me, and no one gets hurt.
把钱交给我  谁也不会受伤
That's right, pay up, keep it coming.
没错  交钱  继续
Sorry, Mr.Judro, sir, but I need the money for my boy Balley.
对不起  朱德罗先生  但我的儿子贝利需要钱
He's been very sick and, uh...
他病得很重  呃
-Oh, son. -Papa!
-哦  儿子  -爸爸
I don't want your excuses.
我不想听你的理由
I want your money.
我想要你的钱